The more I look at you
you seem
like the gay one here
Do you like
Hong Il-tak
or something?
You crazy b******
Stop talking nonsense
I'm doing this because
you keep messing
with Hong Il-tak
It's disgusting
to watch, so stop it
They're gonna
start fighting again
If so…
D***, they're fast
Like cockroaches
If you're fighting
do it without me
I'm so sick of this
F***
Hey, Hong Il-tak
Sit next to me
on the bus later
Okay
Hey, Il-tak
Let's sit together
We have
to talk about the
cross-dressing
contest tonight
- What?
- Huh?
Me?
Yeah
I signed up for you
What?
Next up is the segment
that boasts
our school's tradition…
Even this crappy
school does all this
What am I even
doing here?
The Cross-Dressing
Contest is up next
Hey, you brats…
Fucking hell
At an all-boys' school?
Really?
Don't tell me…
Hello, good morning
evening, night!
The Cross-Dressing
Contest begins now
here at Daemun High
with the greatest
beauties on Earth!
Here's our
first participant!
Give him
a round of applause!
Kim Hyeong-ju
you son of a b****
you moron
you psycho, seriously!
Up next!
Second year, Class 3
Hong Il-tak!
What the f***?
Where is he?
What are you doing
back there?
Could it be…
Lee Hyeon-wu?